<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Vote Connor Coddington</title>
    <link href="https://gatorbear.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://gatorbear.github.io" />
    <updated>2020-04-06T22:43:29-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Connor Coddington</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://gatorbear.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>My Leadership Makes Me a Qualified Candidate Because</title>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Coddington</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gatorbear.github.io/my-leadership-makes-me-a-qualified-candidate-because/"/>
        <id>https://gatorbear.github.io/my-leadership-makes-me-a-qualified-candidate-because/</id>

        <updated>2020-04-06T22:06:57-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://gatorbear.github.io/media/posts/6/IMG_3060.jpeg" alt="" />
                    &hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://gatorbear.github.io/media/posts/6/IMG_3060.jpeg" alt="" />
                <ul>
<li><span >Most Senior SGA officer</span></li>
<li><span >Proposed four constitutional amendments that have been passed by the Senate</span></li>
<li><span >Drafted two resolutions to embody the voice of the student body Senate</span></li>
<li><span >I strive to be available to help my colleagues will also making sure I delegate work out</span></li>
<li><span >Met with every RSO twice while serving as ABC chair</span></li>
<li><span >I am the only current SGA officer who has:</span>
<ul>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Proposed a Constitutional amendment</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Drafted a Resolution</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Served in the Judicial and Legislative branch</span></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><span >During my time at Florida Poly, I have been:</span>
<ul>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Associate Justice</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Judicial Treasurer</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Sophomore Representative</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Audit and Budget Committee Chair</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Junior Representative</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Senate President</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Member of every standing committee of the Senate</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Orientation Leader</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Residential Life Desk assistant</span></li>
<li class="ql-indent-1"><span >Treasurer of the Themed Entertainment Association</span></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title> Why My Vision To Florida Poly Make Me an Excelent Candidate</title>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Coddington</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gatorbear.github.io/why-my-vision-to-florida-poly-make-me-an-excelent-candidate/"/>
        <id>https://gatorbear.github.io/why-my-vision-to-florida-poly-make-me-an-excelent-candidate/</id>

        <updated>2020-04-06T22:17:47-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://gatorbear.github.io/media/posts/5/Screen-Shot-2020-04-06-at-10.17.27-PM.png" alt="" />
                    &hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://gatorbear.github.io/media/posts/5/Screen-Shot-2020-04-06-at-10.17.27-PM.png" alt="" />
                <p><span >If elected, these are some of the goals I will work towards these goals to the best of my ability </span></p>
<p><strong><span >Accessibility</span></strong><span >: Currently, it can be difficult for students not in the Student Government Association to see our information. Agendas and meeting minutes should be easily accessible. More students will know who their leaders are and that we are always available for them.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >Media</span></strong><span >: I want to fund student media to keep students knowledgeable. SGA has a lot to benefit from students staying in the loop.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >Structure</span></strong><span >: The executive branch is the only branch without a handbook. I want to change that. We have an office of standards in enforcement with no written regulation of what tasks they should do. The executive branch should head student news. I will work to create a cabinet from a wide range of Florida Poly Students. Hence, there are many different opinions on different issues.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>My Contributions to Florida Poly Make Me an Excelent Candidate Because</title>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Coddington</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gatorbear.github.io/my-contributions-to-florida-poly-make-me-an-excelent-candidate-because/"/>
        <id>https://gatorbear.github.io/my-contributions-to-florida-poly-make-me-an-excelent-candidate-because/</id>

        <updated>2020-04-06T22:20:51-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://gatorbear.github.io/media/posts/4/Screen-Shot-2020-04-06-at-10.20.39-PM.png" alt="" />
                    &hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://gatorbear.github.io/media/posts/4/Screen-Shot-2020-04-06-at-10.20.39-PM.png" alt="" />
                Throughout my years at Florida Poly, I have done numerous things to contribute to the students. During my Freshman year, I worked with the Judicial Branch as an associate justice to write the Judicial Branch Handbook. During my Sophomore year, I took the role of the Audit and Budget Committee (ABC) chairpersons and made many structural changes. Firstly, I rebuilt the way we audit RSOs and other SGA entities. The new system was more measurable while still giving us a chance for us to see everyone face to face. For the first time, all SGA assets were tracked to help us better understand where our resources were being spent and where new allocations should go. RSO initiatives were conceived to give organizations still adequate funding while having less revenue.<br>Lastly, I worked with ABC to create policies regarding Travel and RSO initiatives. My Sophomore year also focused on working with the leadership of SGA to create our statutes and amend the student body constitution. I proposed three amendments, of which two were drafted into law. This past year, I was elected as Junior Representative and became the Senate President. A significant amount of time has been spent on passing the ordinances that we drafted last year. I worked with different members of the University to make sure the regulations complied with University policies and Florida Law. Following the proposed merger, I drafted a resolution for the student body senate, stating our opposition. In February, I traveled to Tallahassee to represent our position against the proposed bill. We had face-to-face meetings with legislators, delivering copies of the resolution passed by the Senate. I initiated two constitutional amendments that will be on the ballot this year. If I see a need in the student body and I believe SGA can take action, I will do all I can to push it forward.
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
